# **JASON PENG**

Los Angeles, CA 90049

Phone:1-310-780-0860 | Email: jason.j.peng@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/peng-jason/ | Github: https://github.com/JasonJPeng

#### SUMMARY

Web and software developer with industrial experiences in blockchain, engineering, and web hosting. Proficiency in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, PHP, C and SQL. Strength in communication, problem solving, training and customer support. Earned a master degree of Engineering and certificate in Full Stack Web Development from UCLA.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, C, SQL

Applications: blockchain, user interface, engineering, web hosting, database Business skills: programming service, customer service, training, consultancy.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Technical Consultant**The BTC Group
2018 – Present
Los Angeles, CA

Provide technical consulting and programming services in the blockchain related fields.

- Create a voting app on Ethereum blockchain smart contract, using Solidity and JavaScript Web3 integration
- Build a credit report system to track individual's crypto account, using JavaScript, jQuey and PHP
- Build a platform for general users to issue ERC-20 token, using solidity and Javascript
- Integrate CRM (Salesforce) and custodian account system (PrimeTrust)

Owner & Founder 2000 – 2017
WebCubic, Inc. Los Angeles, CA

Founded the company to provide one-stop web services for real estate agents and Realtor Associations.

- Build dynamic, template-based, customizable websites for real estate agents, using PHP and JavaScript
- Provided MLS listing search for customers, using PHP, MySQL and REST API
- Provided web hosting, SEO (search engine optimization), and contents services

## Regional Manager Sherpa Corp,

1996 – 1999

San Jose, CA

Provided programming services to US defense contractors, including JPL, Boeing, Raytheon

- Managed offshore programming service for US companies.
- Provided technical support and training programs to corporate customers
- Programmed in C to customized application's user interfaces and business processes

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Full Stack Web Development: UCLA, Los Angeles, CA

A 3-month intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, Express, & ReactJS.

Master of Engineering: UCLA, Los Angeles, CA

Bachelor of Science: National Taiwan University, Taipei, Taiwan